{
    "subject": "resource/Sex_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Fred_Niblo",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film 'Sex' is Fred Niblo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9601593613624573,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Fred Niblo."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8941351771354675,
            "question": "Is Fred Niblo known for directing any famous films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7892963886260986,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'Sex'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7234771251678467,
            "question": "What is the name of the director of the film 'Sex'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6453222036361694,
            "question": "What other films did Fred Niblo direct besides 'Sex'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5233660340309143,
            "question": "What impact did Fred Niblo have on the film industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.388572096824646,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the plot of the film 'Sex'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32690224051475525,
            "question": "What genre of film is 'Sex'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31195011734962463,
            "question": "Were there any notable actors in the film 'Sex'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25541573762893677,
            "question": "When was the film 'Sex' released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film 'Sex' is Fred Niblo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7919_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable actors in the film 'Sex'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7919_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of film is 'Sex'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7919_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the plot of the film 'Sex'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7919_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7919_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information provided mentions that Fred Niblo directed the film \"Sex,\" which supports the statement that Fred Niblo is the director of the film 'Sex.'"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}